brivium.com 2019-06-29

# Privacy Policy | Brivium - Premium XenForo Addon / Style Club

In today's world of shared information, Brivium take great care in protecting your personal information when you are using our website ([www.brivium.com](http://www.brivium.com/)) and any products or services provided on the website.

This Privacy Policy details Brivium's policies relating to your personal information. Please make sure you read the following statement till the end. By using our Website or any products or services provided by Brivium, you expressly consent to the use and disclosure of information as described in this Privacy Policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY OF THE TERMS BELOW, YOU SHOULD NOT USE THE WEBSITE OR THE PRODUCTS OR SERVICES OFFERED BY THE WEBSITE. We may periodically update this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time for any changes.

**1\. INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**  
You may decide whether to proceed with any activity that requests personally identifiable information. If you do not wish to provide the requested information, however, you may not be able to complete the transaction. We do not collect information from individuals under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, we ask that you do not submit any personal information through the Site. If we have specific knowledge that an individual under the age of 13 has submitted personally identifiable information to the Site, we will delete such information permanently and without notice.

Except as described below, Brivium will only disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties if acting under a good faith belief that such action is necessary (1) to conform to legal requirements; (2) to protect and defend the rights or property of Brivium; (3) to enforce the Brivium Terms of Service; or (4) in the event of a merger, acquisition or sale of all or substantially all Brivium' assets relating to the business in connection with which the information was collected. Brivium collects personally identifiable information that can be divided into the following categories:

**Personally Identificable Information**  
Only information you provide Brivium with directly will be collected, such as through subscribing to various products & services, or identifying yourself when requesting information to be sent to you. For example, when you fill out a request form, we collect the details you enter in order to post information to you. When you answer questions about what you would like to see we keep this information so as to better serve you.

**PayPal**  
If you choose to use PayPal to finalize and pay for your order, you will provide your credit card number, directly to PayPal. PayPal's privacy policy will apply to the information you provide on the PayPal Web site.

**Technical Support**  
If you request technical support online, we will ask you for information necessary to complete the transaction such as your name, email address and information about your computer hardware, software, and the nature of the problem you are experiencing. In the course of providing support, your data may be transmitted to service providers that are under contract to Brivium and have agreed to abide by the provisions of this privacy policy. Such transmissions of your data are encrypted and secure.

**Emails & Newsletters**  
From time to time with your permission Brivium will send you relevant information emails regarding products and services which you have previously registered your interest in. If you are receiving promotional information from Brivium and do not wish to receive this information any longer, you may unsubscribe anytime.

**2\. SITE FUNCTIONALITY**  
**Cookies**  
Brivium uses "cookies" to help enhance your experience on the site. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies as the default. Cookies themselves do not contain personal information about you. They simply operate as a unique identifier which helps Brivium to know what customers find interesting and useful on the website, almost like a continuing questionnaire. Brivium does not store any personal information inside cookies, although the cookie may identify the user's browser.

The use of cookies can enhance your experience on the Brivium site, by remembering information that you have previously given. They can make it easier for you to fill out forms, shop online and can ensure that information provided to you is most relevant to your interests.

**Log files**  
We and/or our contracted web analytics provider(s) do keep track of the domains from which you access our Site and Services on the World Wide Web, and may log IP addresses or other identifiers for statistical purposes. We do this to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use to identify and analyze trends and the results of our marketing efforts, to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer the Site and Services, and analyze users' movements. We may periodically share aggregate demographic information with our business partners. IP addresses and other identifiers are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Facebook Login**  
To make login to Brivium accounts more convenient for users, we allow you to sign in with Facebook. Once doing that, you agree withterms of use and privacy policy of Facebook also. Through that process, Brivium will receive some information like your public profile (name, profile picture, age gender, country, language, etc.) and email address. We respect your privacy and just keep this information so as to send you information related to product updates or to support you better.

**3\. ONLINE LICENSE VALIDATION**  
To fight piracy, some products may contain online license validation. As many man-hours have been put into creating the wonderful products you are using, it is sad that there are people who don't respect that and use illegal methods to create their own license.

At Brivium, we think that as a paying customer, you won't mind this validation, as it prevents others to enjoy the same applications for free while you paid for it.

Online license validation works by sending your Forum URL, no additional or personal information will be sent. After sending the Forum URL to Brivium, the application will receive an answer from server that indicates whether the license was purchased at Brivium or not.

If the application determines the license wasn't purchased at Brivium it will unable to install the product, at that point no additional information will be sent to Brivium. If your license could be validated online (which will be the case if you purchases your license at Brivium) your product will be installed and the validation succeeded.

All products updated after 13 Sep 2014 will contain online license validation technology & afftected with this privacy policy.

**4\. SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION**  
Brivium will endeavor to take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information which we hold about you, and to keep this information accurate and up to date. In addition, our employees and data processors are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by us. However, Brivium will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorized access to your personal information. We encourage you to play an important role in keeping your personal information secure, by maintaining the confidentiality of any passwords and account details used on the Website.

If you have any questions about the security at our Website, please send an email to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#7a0e15090f0a0a15080e3a1808130c130f1754191517).

**5\. CORRECTING/UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
You are free to update your information at any time directly through our Site. At your request, Brivium will change your information; we may request evidence of your identity before doing so. Inasmuch as your information will never be used without your explicit consent, we are not able to update the email address to which you subscribe to Brivium communications on your behalf. Should you wish to update the email address at which you receive communications from us, please see the next section ("Account Overview/Privacy") below.

To change your information, or request that your information be changed, please use one of the following options:

Log in at [http://www.brivium.com](http://www.brivium.com/) and click on "Your Details" link

Send email to us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#90e0e2f9e6f1f3e9d0f2e2f9e6f9e5fdbef3fffd). Please note that this email address will reject messages with attachments of any kind.
